Guide to the Carl Van Vechten Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile, 7.01; 12 boxes
  - Box 187, folder 2476 (Box 321, Folder 4042)
  - Box 187, folder 2482 (Box 321, Folder 4043)
  - Box 187, folder 2483 (Box 321, Folder 4044)
  - Box 187, folder 2484 (Box 321, Folder 4045)
  - Box 187, folder 2491 (Box 321, Folder 4046)
  - Box 187, folder 2493 (Box 321, Folder 4047)
  - Box 187, folder 2494 (Box 321, Folder 4048)
  - Box 187, folder 2500 (Box 321, Folder 4049)
  - Box 188, folder 2505 (Box 321, Folder 4050)
  - Box 235, folder 2715 (Box 321, Folder 4051)
  - Box 298, folder 3134 (Box 321, Folder 4052)
  - Box 179, folder 2293 (Box 322, Folder 4053-4058)
  - Box 180, folder 2299 (Box 322, Folder 4059-4060)
  - World War I clippings, 1914-1918 (Box 323, Folder 4061-4064)
  - Box 184, folder 2375a (Box 324 (Oversize), Folder 4065)
  - Box 187, folder 2465 (Box 324 (Oversize), Folder 4066)
  - Box 187, folder 2471 (Box 324 (Oversize), Folder 4067)
  - Box 187, folder 2478 (Box 324 (Oversize), Folder 4068)
  - Box 276, folder 2838 (Box 324 (Oversize), Folder 4069)
  - Box 280, folder 2926 (Box 324 (Oversize), Folder 4070)
  - Box 280, folder 2927 (Box 324 (Oversize), Folder 4071)
  - Edgar Saltus clippings, 1891-1910 (Box 324 (Oversize), Folder 4072-4073)
- Restricted Papers, 0.42; 1 box
  Box 325, Restricted Papers, is restricted until 2035. For further information consult appropriate curator.